Discover a different breed of hero.
My Little Pony: The Movie is a family, animation,
adventure film directed by Jayson Thiessen.
A new dark force threatens Ponyville, and the Mane 6 – Twilight Sparkle, Applejack, Rainbow Dash, Pinkie Pie, Fluttershy and Rarity – embark on an
unforgettable journey beyond Equestria where they meet new friends and exciting challenges on a quest to use the magic of friendship and save their home.
Twilight Sparkle (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Applejack / Rainbow Dash (voice), played by Ashleigh Ball.
Pinkie Pie / Fluttershy (voice), played by Andrea Libman.
Rarity / Princess Luna / Granny Smith / Derpy Hooves
(voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Spike (voice), played by Cathy Weseluck.
Tempest Shadow / Fizzlepop Berrytwist (voice), played by Emily Blunt.
My Little Pony: The Movie is a 2017 animated musical high fantasy film, directed by Jayson Thiessen and
based on the animated television series My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic by Lauren Faust.
The film features the show's regular voice cast of
Ashleigh Ball, Andrea Libman, Tabitha St.
Germain, Tara Strong, and Cathy Weseluck, along with Uzo Aduba, Emily Blunt, Kristin
Chenoweth, Taye Diggs, Michael Peña, Zoe Saldaña, Liev Schreiber and Sia.
The film follows the flying unicorn Twilight Sparkle, her five pony friends – collectively known as the "Mane Six" – and her
dragon friend and assistant Spike on a quest to save their home of Equestria from an evil conqueror, the Storm King.
My Little Pony: The Movie was produced by Hasbro's Allspark Pictures and animated at DHX Media's
Vancouver division, using traditional animation created using Toon Boom Harmony.
The film premiered in New York City on September 24, 2017, and was
released in the United States on October 6, by Lionsgate.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who criticized the script and pacing, but
praised its animation, voice acting, music and female representation.
It was a box-office success, grossing $61.3 million worldwide against a production budget of
$6.5 million and becoming Lionsgate's highest-grossing animated feature to date.
The film explores themes of friendship, villain, pony, based on toy, journey.
The tone is dark.